[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: Characters, locations, and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only; viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
But this man loves you very much.
I think
you should just say yes.
Thinking about it already gives me a headache.
It was me
who sent those men to get rid of Sarm
Oh.
What the fuck is this shit, huh?!
Jam!
Jam.
That bastard did this to you?
Stop it, Thee!
If you hurt Mr. Sarm in any way,
I will shoot!
How are you?
Are you hurt?
Why should you care at all, Uncle?
I was the one who sent the men to get rid of your son.
Because I know that
at your core...
you're not a bad guy.
I...
I'm truly sorry.
I want to own Adisuan Farm.
I've been wanting to own it for years now.
Half a year ago,
Sarm disappeared.
Everyone knew that he was heartbroken
and wouldn't return soon.
So I used that opportunity
to send men to hunt him down
so that he'd be gone for good.
Then, people would assume that
Sarm was so hurt
that he wanted to live by the sea forever
and had gone missing.
Once the plan came to fruition,
Adisuan Farm would probably belong to me.
No one is better suited to run Adisuan Farm than me.
You also knew that
when Sarm was still away,
I embezzled money,
falsified accounting records,
and forged documents.
I was trying to take over Adisuan Farm bit by bit,
then Sarm came back.
And weren't you aware that
Sarm also knew?
I found it strange myself.
Why did he choose to leave me be despite knowing everything?
Because my son
valued the bond you two shared.
Do you despise me, Uncle?
Do I?
I don't, actually.
Whether or not...
I'd forgive you, though?
It's still too soon.
Do you know what the consequences
of your action are?
Let this
be a lesson to you.
Every day
is a chance to start over.
Rest well.
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself, not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you, no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart, lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
Jam.
Mr. Sarm?
Little Jam...
Little Jam!
Sarm, Sarm.
Calm down, calm down.
Song,
is Little Jam safe?
He is safe
and has been treated.
Rest easy, okay?
He's in the waiting room right now.
PiMai is trying to make him feel better.
What time is it?
It's almost 5 A.M.
Am I hurt that badly?
Why am I hospitalized?
You're having another brain scan.
Huh?
It's to see if anything's wrong.
Do I even have that thing?
Knock, knock.
Seems like you don't.
That's why you were being so reckless.
You almost lost your head, alright?
Being my twin brother,
you always scold me or say nasty things to me.
I'm a tiger with nine lives, alright?
Right.
I don't go down that easily.
I hope that's true.
Come on, you already know
that I'm...
tough.
You people don't sleep or what?
You already knew it, didn't you?
I did.
You mean I'm handsome, right?
Not that, damn it!
You knew that it was Thee who sent men to hunt you down, right?
Of course...
Fine!
I'll say it.
I found out when I got captured the second time.
That night...
I came back to my place with Little Jam after dinner,
and they were already waiting for me.
Then, I thought to myself,
"How can I trace this back to the person behind it?"
So I pretended to let them capture me.
They tried taking me to a deserted island,
but I didn't let them.
I fought back.
I beat them up!
Punched!
Slammed!
Hit!
And punched!
Mm!
Then, they folded.
They spit it out, telling me that
it was Thee...
who gave them the order.
Curse you, Thee...
If I hadn't been worried about Little Jam,
I would've punched,
hit,
slammed,
and punched them more!
So luck was on their side, huh?
Mm...
So I quickly backtracked
and jumped into the water.
I swam, swam, swam.
"Little Jam!
Where are you, Little Jam?!"
And I found him floating in the middle of the sea.
I asked myself...
"Would he be okay?"
So I swam him back to the shore.
We ended up on Ko Samui.
As for them,
I pressured
and squeezed them
until they became key witnesses
that would then seal Thee's fate.
I simply have to call them,
and they will make a grand reveal!
It'll be glorious!
And majestic!
Oh...
But it was too little, too late.
Sheesh...
I didn't get to be the star of the show.
It's because of you, Sib.
You sent Little Jam on a mission like that.
And how did it go?
Just look at this mess...
I didn't know that you knew.
That's why I sent Jam to look for evidence
so that we can do it by the book.
I didn't know that you knew.
You should've told me what you were doing.
What about Dad?
Did he know anything?
He told me that
Uncle Mai was his friend
back when they served in the army in the South.
Ever since Uncle Mai found you at the beach,
he has always been keeping Dad posted.
Uncle Mai...
The owner of the seafood restaurant?
I never knew that.
Oh, Uncle Mai.
Whoa... You were pretty slick.
And if I knew that Dad knew,
I wouldn't have sent Jam
to bring you back in the first place.
None of us ever talk to one another, do we?
And what about you?
Hm?
Did you know anything at all?
I think I kind of did,
but...
I wasn't sure.
Thought so.
And...
And what are we going to do about Thee?
I'm taking this all the way.
Bad guys don't get happy endings.
The word "forgiveness"
is not
in my dictionary!
Don't teach me what it means either.
Thee, who I loved like a brother
and trusted with everything,
is now but a ghost!
And I don't want to see his face at Adisuan Farm again.
You, my brother...
love someone deeply when you do
and despise the person when you hate them.
You've always been like this since you were a kid.
Normally,
I'd rush to my little boy.
But this isn't normal.
I'm still upset with him.
I've asked him time and time again,
yet he always hides the truth from me.
I won't just be mad at him for a week,
because this time...
I'll be mad at him for months! Just you wait!
Why didn't you listen?!
You're so stubborn!
Mr. Sarm...
Hold it right there!
Not now.
Your mission has ended.
This evening...
It's time for you to return to Bangkok.
Understood.
I'm here to return your glasses.
Thank you.
Your phone and your car key...
Right.
Your car will be brought over tomorrow.
No need to drive it yourself.
I'll have someone drive it to you.
But...
No buts.
Hello.
Escort Mr. Jam to his place.
Drive as smoothly as you can.
Do not go over 80 km/h.
Report back to me once you reach the destination.
Do not forget to warn him to wear a seat belt
because he's just that stubborn.
He refuses to listen.
And don't eat
instant noodles too often.
Eat some actual food.
Mm.
Don't overwork yourself.
Can't keep working round the clock like this.
Get some rest.
Wherever you go,
keep your eyes peeled.
I know that you've got this,
but nobody's there to take care of you
when you're living there alone.
As for boiled crabs...
the ones from here are the best.
Do not forget to take care of yourself, too.
I should be happy because I'm done with Mr. Sarm.
But why is it the opposite?
I haven't gotten to ask him to be my boyfriend
or wrap myself up as his present.
Why?
Just why?
Look...
This is Mr. Croc, my beloved crocodile plush.
I love him so much.
Can I bring Mr. Croc to Pak Chong with me?
Why did your boss send you here?
To learn the ins and outs of this farm.
Are you sure?
Don't hide anything from me.
Mm.
Okay.
I believe you.
Are you sure you actually lost?
Mm.
Are you certain
that you're not plotting anything?
I am doing nothing.
I'll give you one more chance.
Spit it out.
I said I wasn't plotting anything.
Okay.
But if I catch you lying,
even if it's you,
I won't let it slide.
Why?
If I really am hiding something from you...
That was just a hypothetical situation
and nothing else.
I'd be furious.
I'd be mad at you for a whole week.
You can be mad at me for a week if you want,
but you have to forgive me after that, okay?
Look at you...
What a mess.
This man...
He's worn out...
Not that big of a deal.
Huh?
"Not that big of a deal?"
You did this to yourself, Sarm.
I think
"not that big of a deal is different for everyone."
Someone I trusted...
sent his men to get rid of me.
Ow...
I think I've developed
trust issues.
I can no longer trust anyone.
Hey...
I'm sorry.
I...
I forgot about that.
Listen...
And out of nowhere,
Little Jam...
was sent here.
I always
had my suspicions about him.
I asked
what his goal was,
but I never got an answer!
He just kept dodging my questions...
I asked him so many times, too.
He had no intention of hiding it from you, Sarm.
It's Sib.
He was following our big brother's order.
Listen.
I'm
upset at both of them.
But I'm mad at them for different reasons.
Look at this plush.
Just look at it.
It's staring at me like this.
I'm in this state,
and yet you dare stare at me?
You dare keep staring at me?
What?!
Got beef with me?!
You're not going to feel sorry
or show any remorse at all?
What is it, huh?!
How do you want to settle this?!
What was that for?
Go away.
But with Little Jam, you see...
Mm.
I...
I didn't quit trying.
My feelings toward him haven't changed.
I'm just confused.
But...
Why did he...
He didn't even try to make it up to me?
You want Jam to make it up to you?
But you always looked...
extremely unfriendly toward him.
Gosh...
Given the situation,
how am I supposed to keep smiling?
I can't.
I simply can't.
And what are you feeling exactly?
Are you angry?
Furious?
Sad?
Or upset?
All of the above.
Mm.
I...
I don't know.
I'm feeling all of them at once.
If I were a bowl of spicy salad,
I'd be one with everything in it.
Even if I got mad at him,
he wouldn't make it up to me.
I'm so upset...
You love Jam, don't you?
Of course, I do.
I love Little Jam.
I love him so much.
I love him more than anyone.
Hey.
I, Traiphop,
love Jiranat
forever.
If you love him,
why did you let your emotions
take over?
What should I do, then?
If I were you,
I wouldn't wait around any longer.
We're all grownups now.
Don't complicate things.
If you miss him,
just say it.
If you want to hear his voice,
just call him.
Or...
If you want to see him,
just go see him.
It's as simple as that.
Mm...
Thank you very much, Song.
It's like you've experienced it before.
Who did that to you?
It's okay.
You've still got me.
Listen, I'm right here.
I'm here...
- Let me kiss you. - It's okay...
- I'm good... - Come here.
Stupid Sarm.
You should feel sorry about yourself first.
Take a look at yourself.
You're like a wet dog.
Aunt Nim made you five-spice stew in a tiffin box.
Don't forget to eat the stew.
Right.
You can go now.
See you.
What is it now?
What's wrong?
You didn't tell me sweet dreams.
"Sweet dreams"?
Am I Jam or what?
Don't mention that name.
There, there, there.
It's okay. It's okay.
Okay, well, then...
Sweet dreams.
Good night, good night.
Okay...
Good night.
Bye-bye.
I'm leaving now, okay?
See you, alright?
Again?
You've stopped kissing me on the head.
A kiss on my head! Come on!
A kiss on your head?
You used to do it every night.
Fine, come here.
Here comes a kiss on the head.
Here comes your kiss on the head...
Better now?
Yes, you can leave now...
- Better? - Mm.
Bye-bye.
You've been extremely weird since you were a kid.
Don't forget that
we're twins.
If I'm weird,
then so are you.
Oh, you.
You, of all people...
are such a pain.
Damn you, Sarm!
Bye.
I'm leaving for real now.
Right.
I miss you, Little Jam!
Little Jam...
I miss you...
Little Jam.
Oh, Little Jam...
Little Jam...
Little Jam, I miss you.
Little Jam!
Whoa.
This house is full of scary animals.
Little Jam!
Your house is very lovely, you know?
♫I came this far just to meet you♫
♫There's so much you've been through♫
♫But that doesn't matter♫
♫Time stood still when I met you♫
♫The way you gazed at me too♫
Are you hitting on me?
Yes, just now realizing that?
♫I came this far just to meet you♫
♫There's so much you've been through♫
♫But that doesn't matter♫
♫Mend your heart, make it better♫
♫Whatever it is, you don't need to fear,♫
♫For I'll be right here by your side like always♫
♫It seems like something's moving♫
♫What's in my heart isn't too much, but I only♫
You silly...
I already miss you just watching this.
Everything looks perfectly normal.
Little Jam!
Whoa, Mr. Sarm?!
- Little Jam! - How did you get here?
Little Jam...
Hey...
No matter what I do,
where I go,
or where I look,
I always see his face.
Juju.
What should I do?
I cannot stop thinking about Mr. Sarm.
How are you guys doing?
Why did you ask that question?
So what if I'm doing well?
And what if I'm not?
Are you going to cut my salary?
I'd like to make it clear that
I will not let you cut my salary.
The only thing that can be cut
is my love for you!
You can't just be hangry and take it on me.
Anything else you want?
It's on me.
No need to treat me to anything, Sarm.
Why is that?
It's because I can treat myself.
Right...fantastic.
Do you love Jam, Sarm?
Yes,
I love Jam.
I knew it...
The night at the New Year party,
when you two kissed,
I accidentally saw it.
Mm...
It has been clear since then.
Tell Jam to shower you with love
and love you as much as I've been hurt!
Are you okay?
It doesn't matter anymore.
It's okay if our love got cut short.
At least my priority was making good memories together,
even if you didn't choose me.
I'll have to take my leave now.
Then I'll go with him.
Wait, Mr. Wasin.
You invited me here.
And...
Since when am I out of the loop?
Uh...
Back at the New Year party,
Lantao dressed as a medium
to exorcise ghosts.
But he exorcised the wrong ghost.
I'll be seeing you soon.
Oh...
This is just great.
Lantao
is about to make history.
Oh?
Oh, Ning-nong.
I have something to tell you, Sarm.
What is it?
So...
Someone's asking about buying the horse again.
The horse's got serious charm,
like the one who raised it.
I'm not selling it.
Would you like to have dinner now, Mr. Sarm?
What's for dinner?
There's rice porridge,
stir-fried morning glory,
salted squid heads,
spicy salad with salted eggs,
roasted prawns glazed with toddy palm sugar,
and sweet fried dried fish.
I'll have fried rice with crabs.
Absolutely.
I'll prepare it right away.
We're all grownups now.
Don't complicate things.
If you miss him, just go see him.
It's as simple as that.
If I miss him...
I should go see him?
Aunt.
Yes?
I'll have dinner later.
"If I miss him...
I should go see him."
"If I miss him... I should go see him."
I miss him!
I miss him!!
Juju!
Is that you, Juju?
Juju, it's your papa.
I've come in peace.
Juju!
How was your time at the cat hotel, Juju?!
Do you want to take a trip to Pak Chong?!
We've got horses
and goats.
You'll get to go on a trip with us!
Juju!
Oh, Juju!
Don't say no just yet!
Turn around, please!
Help me out, please!
Juju...
Jam.
Jam...
Little Jam!
Ow...
Little Jam,
it's me, Sarm.
Am I missing him so much
that I'm imagining him here?
Little Jam!
Give me a break.
Ow...
Come on, Juju.
Shall we go to bed together?
Little Jam!
This is Sarm...
It's me.
- Mr. Sarm?! - Damn right!
I mean, yes.
It's me.
- Wait, wait, wait. - Yes?
What are you doing?!
I'm...
I'm here to see you, Little Jam.
Gosh...
Get off the gate...
There's so little time left.
I've got something to tell you.
I
miss
you,
Jam!
Mr. Sarm!
Little Jam...
Get down from there right now.
No...
I can't wait any longer,
not even another second.
It feels heavy,
so I need to get it off my chest.
Ow, uh...
- Hey, get down. - Get down from there!
- What? I... - Get down!
- Get down! - Down, now!
- Hey! - Get down from there!
- Let me go! - What are you doing?
You can't.
I haven't done anything wrong!
You're trespassing.
Little Jam...
Little Jam.
Do you want us to call the police, Mr. Jam?
Please take care of him, Poj.
Right.
No, you can't. I'm staying here.
I won't leave.
I'm not leaving.
- I'm not leaving here. - Mister...
- No, please, don't do it... - Don't... Don't resist.
- Don't... - Don't resist. Come with us.
I'm not leaving.
Whatever you see fit, Poj.
This just in!
I would like to explain.
I did it because my heart told me to do so.
[Traiphop Reveals: He Was Following His Heart]
I confess!
I did it because my heart couldn't take it anymore. [He Claims He Couldn't Take It Anymore]
I beg Jiranat to listen to me! [He Begs Jiranat to Listen to Him]
I deny it!
I never intended to trespass.
I admit it!
I'm willing to do whatever it takes to have you back.
I repeat!
I love you!
I love you every single second!
I love you with every breath I take!
Listen...
I love you.
What should we do with him?
Take him away, Poj.
Huh?!
Come with us.
Now!
- Move! - Little Jam!
Move it... Now.
- Jam... - Come with us.
My partner and I have a bit of a misunderstanding.
Mr. Jam is single!
Everyone knows that.
Even ghosts do!
Not true.
Mr. Jam told us to do whatever we see fit,
but we won't report you to the police
if you agree to never trespass again.
Okay, I agree.
Okay.
I won't do it again. I promise you.
Cross my heart.
I won't do it again.
But we won't let you go
until someone can vouch for you and say you won't do it again.
Okay.
Fine.
I,
Traiphop,
will vouch for myself.
- Not allowed! - You can't!
I can't?
Fine, then.
I want to get my phone.
Mr. Sib...
I've been arrested.
Is this okay?
He's my brother.
It's Sib.
Okay.
We'll take our leave now.
Right.
- Hey... - That's enough, Sarm.
Calm down and think about
what you've done.
Well, when you miss someone, you miss them.
I shouldn't have...
Shouldn't have saved me?
I shouldn't have sent Jam to bring you back.
Can I talk to you for a second?
What?
Little Jam!
Why did you do that?
Little Jam.
Little Jam...
Hey.
Yes?
You came all the way here to see me...
What do you need?
You. I miss you.
I thought he had something urgent, coming here at this hour.
If you want to see me,
do not climb the gate again.
Oh...
You're worried about me?
I am worried about the gate.
Okay.
It is getting late now.
You should leave.
I'll be on my way, then.
Then, I'll see you again.
But do not climb the gate again.
I promise you.
Next time,
I'll climb the gate faster and better.
Mr. Sarm.
No,
I was kidding.
Okay, I promise you.
You should leave now.
Head inside first, then.
You have to leave when I head inside, okay?
Bye-bye.
Have a safe trip.
Bye-bye...
Bye-bye.
Bye...
Whoa!
Crazy guy.
Why did you have climb the gate?
Do you think you are Spider-Man or what?
[Good night, Jam]
You silly.
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou♫
Are you sick, Little Jam?
I'm worried.
I can sleep on the couch.
I'm easygoing,
not a picky eater.
Meow.
And I'm low-maintenance.
I'll take you scuba diving to see the beautiful coral
and sea anemones.
I have to leave early tomorrow.
♫Kiss, kiss♫
♫You♫
♫Can I kiss you?♫
♫Kiss, kiss♫
♫That's all I've ever wanted♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss? (Ohhhh, oh)♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss? (Just you, only you, can it be you?)♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more (Hoo, woo)♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie (Hoo, woo)♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou (If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind)♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou, ou (If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind)♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
[Your Third Series]